export const DoubleJeopardy = [
  [
    'Lists',
    'That\'s What She Said Setups',
    'Goofing Off',
    'Cold Opens',
    'Random',
    'Randomness: The Sequel',
  ],
  {
    question: 'List 3 DM branches other than Scranton',
    answer:
      'Akron, Albany, Nashua, Rochester, Utica, Syracuse, Binghamton, Buffalo, Camden, Northeast, Pittsfield, Stamford, Yonkers',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question: 'Youâ€™ve always left me satisfied and smiling',
    answer: 'Jim | Michael',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question: 'What are Sabre\'s version of PostIt notes called?',
    answer: 'StickyQuips',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question: 'What beverage of Jim\'s does Stanley drink without noticing?',
    answer: 'Orange juice',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What item has Erin never owned because there is always one around?',
    answer: 'Toothbrush',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Gabe\'s middle name?',
    answer: 'Susan',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },

  {
    question: 'List 4 of Andy\'s wrong answers for the Kit Kat theme song.',
    answer:
      'Football cream, Fancy Feast, Apple Sauce, Chysler Car, Lumber Tar, Snickers Bar, Grey Poupon, Claude Van Damme, hair for men, poison gas, nutrasweet',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question: 'Dwight, get out of my nook!',
    answer: 'Kelly | Pam',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What did Pam name "Box of paper snowshoe racing" during the office olympics?',
    answer: 'Flonkerton',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question: 'Jan didn\'t make Michael breakfast but she did do this.',
    answer: 'She bought the milk',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question:
      'If you asked Creed, who didn\'t show up for the spot check at the mill in the "Watermark" episode?',
    answer: 'Debbie Brown',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What kind of trophy did Kelly receive for the Spicy Curry award at the Dundies?',
    answer: 'Bowling',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question: 'List 2 of the 4 fake diseases Jim and Pam submit to Dwight.',
    answer:
      'Spontaneous Dental Hydroplosion, Government Created Killer Nanorobot Infection, Hotdog Fingers, Count Choculitis',
    answered: false,
    value: 1200,
  },
  {
    question: 'Does the skin look red and swollen? ',
    answer: 'Doctor | Dwight',
    answered: false,
    value: 1200,
  },
  {
    question: 'Who will wait for no one when they knock at your door?',
    answer: 'The KGB',
    answered: false,
    value: 1200,
    dailyDouble: true,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What creative way to get from place to place do Michael, Dwight, and Andy practice at the office?',
    answer: 'Parkour',
    answered: false,
    value: 1200,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Princess Unicorn\'s catch phrase?',
    answer: 'My horn can pierce the sky',
    answered: false,
    value: 1200,
  },
  {
    question:
      'Where did Deangelo\'s assistant Jordyn work before she started at DM?',
    answer: 'Anthropologie',
    answered: false,
    value: 1200,
  },
  {
    question: 'List 3 DM Christmas Party Themes',
    answer:
      'Pennsylvania Dutch Christmas, Moroccan Christmas, Mo Rocca Christmas, Classy Christmas, Honalulu Christmas, Pulp Fiction Christmas, Muslim Christmas',
    answered: false,
    value: 1600,
  },
  {
    question: 'Why is this so hard?',
    answer: 'Jan | Jan',
    answered: false,
    value: 1600,
  },
  {
    question: 'Dwight goes to the mall to recreate a sceen from what movie?',
    answer: 'Pretty Woman',
    answered: false,
    value: 1600,
  },
  {
    question: 'What does Pam buy of Dwight\'s out of the vending machine?',
    answer: 'Pencil cup',
    answered: false,
    value: 1600,
  },
  {
    question:
      'During trivia night at a bar, one of the correct answers was Albert Einstein. What was The Einstein\'s answer to that question?',
    answer: 'Thomas Edison',
    answered: false,
    value: 1600,
    dailyDouble: true,
  },
  {
    question: 'What does Creed grow in his desk?',
    answer: 'Mung beans',
    answered: false,
    value: 1600,
  },
  {
    question: 'List 4 of Dwight\'s Friends',
    answer: 'Trevor, Rolf, Wolf, Gabor, Ziek, Melvina, Mose, Nate',
    answered: false,
    value: 2000,
  },
  {
    question: 'Comedy is a place where the mind goes to tickle itself',
    answer: 'David Brent | David Brent',
    answered: false,
    value: 2000,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the band that sings Deangelo\'s juggling song?',
    answer: 'Evanescence',
    answered: false,
    value: 2000,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the trick to Kevin\'s famous chili?',
    answer: 'Undercook the onions',
    answered: false,
    value: 2000,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Deangelo\'s full name?',
    answer: 'Deangelo Jeremitrius Vickers',
    answered: false,
    value: 2000,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What Scranton Strangler linked item does Michael think his grandkids will be able to sell in order to buy a spaceship?',
    answer: 'Jar of gravel',
    answered: false,
    value: 2000,
  },
];
